This is unexpected. Uh-huh.
Interesting.
I guess I made a mistake in assuming
it would have been long dead by now.
Looks like you screwed up the
delivery you were supposed to make.
I take it you're the one who
asked him to deliver this?
Nah, I'm just a hired hand.
Don't tell me you're the one who did that.
Uh, yeah, that's all on me.
I'm really sorry, I didn't
know it was so important.
No need to apologize.
I could not care less about
whatever the shipment was.
My business is with the little
one standing behind you.
You see, it's my responsibility.
to locate it and bring it back with me.
That sure is mighty generous of you
to come all this way to help him out.
Yeah, that kid is worth more to
me than you could even imagine.
Where the heck did that come from, man?
I'll warn you not to get in my way.
Now, you mind handing the
little fella over to me?
We are still talking about Rolo, right?
I don't know his name.
The kid behind you.
He's worth some real money.
Well, his carcass at least.
Wait, what did you just say?
You want his carcass?
I guess I could bring it back alive
and let my client have some fun.
But the kid would be nothing but trouble.
It's like I'm doing
them a favor, you know?
I really don't understand
what you're talking about.
You don't have to understand.
Perry!
What is happening?
Both Noor and that man are moving
so fast, I can't see a thing!
Lady Lindbergh, you are not
to leave my side, understand?
You know, you're kind of
a weird one, aren't you?
Perry!
You're slowing me down.
So, I'll just have to lop your
head right off, I suppose.
This is unbelievable!
Just one strike with that tiny
blade, it's ridiculously strong!
Kind of like that cow I fought before.
Or maybe even stronger than that.
Like I said, you're weird.
This is bad.
All I can do is avoid him
on my intuition alone.
Fighting him while protecting Rolo
is going to wear me down eventually.
Friend, you are irritating me.
The intensity is unreal.
I can't get any closer.
It is!
This situation is
treacherous, so stand back.
If we get too close, we
could be swept up in it.
There is no mistaking who that is.
I know that face.
He is the Dead Man.
The Dead Man?
Former S-Rank adventurer, Dead Man Zadu.
Dead Man Zadu?
Ah, yes, I agree.
That would be fine.
Pardon me.
I thought that you were supposed to be
helping out with the guards today, Ines.
I was, and I came across
this while doing so.
They're documents from an unsolved case.
It is written here,
intended target is dead.
So why do we act as if it's still ongoing?
Yes, that problem is over and done with.
Officially, the target is
already considered dead.
Officially?
Dandog speaks of Dead Man Zadu.
At an incredibly young age, he
became an S-Rank adventurer,
and then proceeded to become
a target for other S-Ranks.
There is officially a human S-Rank target.
Sounds like a great deal of fun.
I'd love to take a guy
like him down for you.
No, you won't.
I would strongly recommend
not fighting him.
Yes, that's a much smarter move.
What is this?
He's so bad that he
scares the instructors?
Let me see those documents you got there.
It's more like...
Zadu keeps defeating everyone.
We don't want to send more
people just to get killed.
Precisely.
I fail to see any benefit in us going to
battle with that can of worms right now.
Are you curious?
Yeah.
As a young boy.
he managed to master the complexities
of the ancient art of dwarven alchemy.
And at the tender age of 13, he had
already earned the name Dragonslayer.
At the age of 13?
You mean he was better than me?
His abilities continued to
be recognized after that,
as his reputation spread to foreign lands.
He had become the very
apex of all adventurers.
The way that you're talking
about this guy makes
him seem like he's the
perfect fairy tale hero.
How did such an accomplished
person become a target?
Despite all his natural skills,
he did not always use his abundance of
talents and techniques for the right things.
It's just as written there.
36 members of a merchant
family of Sorenza all murdered.
He used his skills to
kill ordinary people?
Yes, and because of that,
some in the guild association suggested he
be stripped of his adventurer's license.
but all the contributions he has made to
the guild were seen as far too significant.
He took down a disaster-level
threat of a monster all on his own.
Ultimately,
because the opinion of how to deal
with Zadu was so greatly divided,
the matter was thus put
on an indefinite hold.
That man accepts any and every commission
without any form of discrimination.
Well, that is, if the price is right.
Morals, social etiquette,
history, or precedence,
they are all completely
meaningless to him.
The examples are vast and disturbing.
He wiped out an entire country.
As his client requested, he destroyed
their entire army all on his own.
and then murdered the
whole of the royal family.
It was as if he had merely
stepped on an anthill.
Before long, people began to realize.
It was like he had absolutely no concept
of what is good and what is evil.
Zadu once had a massive
bounty on his head.
And was challenged by
multitudes of adventurers.
But even as the reward
grew higher and higher.
It only ended in a mountain of corpses.
In order to prevent any
more meaningless casualties.
The guild announced
publicly that he was killed.
And now he's beyond redemption.
Ah, well, damn it.
Tell me, how did you do that?
How did you just destroy
most of my collection?
I'm sorry that I broke them all,
but it's kind of your fault for just
attacking us out of nowhere, you know?
Oh, no, I am not expecting an apology.
But I'm curious.
I can understand Mithril, but Aurichalcum
and Dragontusk don't break that easily.
They're both extremely durable.
Oh, my bad.
I can pay you back.
Like I said, you're a pretty
weird guy, aren't you?
And maybe even weirder is that big sword
you have a weird guy with a weird sword.
Well, whatever, I'll
just play it safe then!
And use this baby instead.
Dear God, his one sword splits
apart into scores of others.
And in the blink of an eye,
hundreds of lives are taken.
A deadly weapon he
transmuted by his own hand.
I bring you the Silver Cross!
Destroy as many of them as you like.
It won't matter I can make
as many of them as I want
Destroying as many of them
as you like it won't matter.
I can make as many of them as I want
Instructor I knew I
couldn't handle all of them.
This is not good.
He has conjured countless
silver crosses at this rate.
All of us will be killed.
He needs my help.
I must compose myself.
My mission is to make sure Lady
Lindberg makes it safely into exile.
I need to calmly determine my priorities
and take stock of what I need to do.
Lady Lindbergh, may I have your permission
to leave you and assist in the battle?
Let's try that again.
Countering is the best I can manage.
I'm too late for these!
Divine Shield!
Heck yeah!
Parry!
My duty as Divine Shield is to
protect Lady Lindbergh at all costs.
Which is precisely why.
I will not, under any
circumstance, let this man die.
Sorry for the wait, I'm here now.
Ines, you're amazing!
Divine Shield!
That shield of light
is almost like a sword.
Though it doesn't seem
like any will hit him.
And his silver blades are
still slipping through somehow.
This isn't working.
Nothing will change if we
continue fighting like this.
I will focus on defense
for the time being.
Okay, Noor.
Do you think you can take this guy out?
It's a swarm of blades flying around
like a living creature but hey i
remember hitting a bird once that was
faster than this oh the fang of that frog
maybe this will work in this can you
do it hmm yeah on my signal remove only
the shields that are right in front of
me are you sure this is going to work.
Maybe, I don't know, but
we're about to find out.
Physical enhancement.
Now!
Don't throw!
The silver crosses are shattering.
Did he throw the Black Death
Dragon's nails and fangs?
Don't worry, I've got plenty of ammo,
so I'll just keep throwing away.
Okay.
Don't throw!
Instructor.
I've taken out a lot of them.
Just a few more.
Perry!
That was a close one.
You kind of surprised me that time.
I could say the same about you.
How did you block that one so quickly?
Also, this one's adamantite.
How in the world did you manage
to break something so resilient?
Oh man, I apologize.
But you were all coming at me and stuff.
I said before, I don't need an apology.
But I will have to make
up for what I've lost.
Could you please stop it with
all the surprise attacks?
And there's that weird
sword being weird again.
You two are truly made for one another.
How have you been able to see every single
one of my attacks and
then use it to counter?
I just do.
I feel like there must be much more
to it than such a blasé answer.
You're gonna try it again, aren't you?
I'm good.
It's a pain in the ass to recover Mithril
after it gets shattered
all over the place,
so I think I'll close up shop for the day.
So then, you're leaving
now, right? Yes, yes.
Although I heard there's going to be a
flashy celebration in the royal capital,
but I guess I'll probably have
to give up going to that, too.
What do you mean there's a
celebration in the capital?
I don't know all the details, but it
sounds like it'll be a real hootenanny.
Now then, it's been a swell time,
but I guess I'll just pack it up.
Be seeing ya, you big weirdo. Okay, bye.
Tell me, how did you get to be so weird?
Why do you keep saying that to me?
I don't think I'm a weirdo.
In my line of work, I've met a lot
of strange people along the way,
but among them all, I can say
you're exceptionally screwy.
Consider yourself lucky, demon folk.
I could have made a good haul
bringing you back with me.
What a way.
However, hurry!
Could you please just give it a rest?
Can't really have any fun with
this guy around now, can we?
Did Zadu say that there would be some
sort of celebration in the royal capital?
Yes.
Oh, cool.
You two want to check it out?
Sounds like it'll be quite the party.
I am curious.
I wonder what's happening.
Yeah, well, in that case, why don't we
go back and hang out for a little while?
Huh?
You know what?
We're really not that far from the city.
Besides, we can't take
Rolo all the way to Mithra.
I mean, it'll take us way
too long to get there.
But, Zornor, I'm not sure that...
No, we can't do it.
What's wrong?
Are you getting cold?
You don't look too good.
Um, did you say you all
came from the royal capital?
Yeah.
Since we can't all go on our journey,
I thought we could just go back.
What's the matter, Rolo?
Do you not want to come
with us or something?
Oh, sorry.
That isn't it.
You can't...
You cannot go back there.
What do you mean by that?
I overheard something.
The biggest of them is
going to the royal capital.
It's said to be strong enough
to wipe out the entire city.
They've been planning
something for months.
They said it'll make the Black
Death Dragon look like nothing.
What do you mean, wipe out the city?
Ines, we need to get back to the capital.
This situation appears more
urgent than we thought.
Instructor, are you okay with that?
Well, yeah, of course I am.
You need to wait.
I cannot agree to this.
Lord Rain told me that I need to...
I know.
He told you that if anything happens in
the capital, to escape with me to Mithra.
That is what he told you to do, correct?
How do you know about that?
I'm his little sister.
I know how my brother
thinks when it comes to me.
And besides, I couldn't live with
being the only one who ran away.
And of course, somebody
needs to tell them.
They must know about
the danger they're in.
But, m 'lady! Inez, please!
You know the story of the demon folk
and how they lost their homeland, right?
Even if we try to escape now, we will only
end up with the same fate as they did.
As you wish.
We shall all go to the capital.
But please, Lady Lindbergh, do not,
under any circumstances, leave my side.
Thank you for doing this, Ines.
Rolo, what do you want to do?
If you really don't want to go there with
us, probably best if we part ways here.
I will go too.
Because whoever is bringing that dragon,
we can be sure they must be demon folk.
Oh, that's right.
Being demon folk sounds like hard work.
I'm sure knowing this boy's
upbringing has greatly pained Noor.
He's such a big-hearted person.
At least compared to me.
I sure wish I could have had
myself a plate of that poison frog.
Ah, well.
Honestly, it would be a
lie to say I'm not worried.
But if Instructor Noor,
who fought off both a black death dragon
and the legendary dead man Zadu is with us,
then maybe we'll be okay.
Hey, Rolo, look.
Check out the wild horses over there.
Uh, yeah.
Right.
As princess of Clay's kingdom,
my duty is to the people.
I must bring him.
This man who jumped straight
out of an epic hero's tale.
He must go back to the royal capital.
Even if it costs me my life.
We need to hurry.
Get there as quickly as possible.
Reporting in sir,
most of the citizens in the old city
district have been successfully evacuated.
Well done,
the efforts of the sovereign six have paid
off and I believe they
have fended off the.
Enemy's ambush right there should
still be another wave coming,
the secret corps have been conducting.
A desperate search for the enemy sir,
but there has been no sign of them.
If they're coming they will do it now.
Our forces have all been scattered.
They're waiting for us
to exhaust ourselves.
If they're smart, they should
be setting up for the next big
wave. Probably so.
The problem is, we cannot even
fathom exactly what the next
wave will be.
Nor from what direction.
The north?
The south?
Or maybe?
According to The hunter
corps' latest report,
there have been no
confirmed sightings of any.
Flying beast
what
is that
oh you see that something
is hovering up there
just above the clouds.
Uncover
My god.
This cannot be happening.
It's a black dragon!
That's not what this is.
This is far too big for that. Oh no.
This is a dragon of calamity.
. . .
.
I'm not going to break all my dreams.
I'm not going to be alive.
I'm not going to be able to show you.
I can't keep it away from the other way.
It's not a chance for me.
I'm not going to be able to give up.
I'm not going to be able to hear you.
It's not going to be able to hear you.
Oh?